Guide to the Reston Reflections oral history collection, 1994-2009
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Transcripts, 1994-2008; (79 boxes)
  - Edwards, Abbie, June 1, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Edwards, Abbie, June 1, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Edwards, Abbie, June 7, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Edwards, Abbie, June 5, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Edwards, David, 2000s (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Edwards, David, May 29, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    512.24
  - Edwards, Jan, January 5, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    504.44
  - Elder, Jim, December 22, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Elder, Jim, June 3, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Elliott, April, May 16, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Ellis, Steve, April 15, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    518.20
  - Espino, Jose, May 15, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Espino, Jose, May 15, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Espino, Jose, May 17, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Estabrook, James, May 8, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Eun, May 28, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Eurich, Barbara, 2000s (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Everhart, William, May 6, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Every, Joy, June 5, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Farah, April 29, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    516.1
  - Farrell, Theresa, May 12, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Farrell, Theresa, May 11, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    512.26
  - Fauber, Kevin, February 17, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Faubert, Eduardo, June 9, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Faubert, Eduardo, May 7, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Faubert, Eduardo, April 12, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    515.22
  - Fedorko, Robert, June 8, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Fellows, Susan, 2000s (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Fellows, Susan, June 10, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Fellows, Susan, June 9, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Fields, Martha, May 21, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Finley, Thomas, May 31, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Findley, Ellen, May 24, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Fisher, Wes, March 29, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    515.29
  - Fleeter, Thomas, April 29, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Fliess, Maurice, May 27, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    512.28
  - Flynn, Madeline, June 11, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Flynn, Madeline, June 11, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Flynn, Thomas, January 12, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Ford, Terrence, May 10, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Forner, George, December 29, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    452.34
  - Forst, Judith, June 5, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Forst, Judith, June 6, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Fossett, Gary, May 10, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Fosset, Gary, May 10, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Foster, Stephen, June 5, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Foster, Gary, May 2, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Foster, Christine, April 12, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    516.24
  - Foster, Norman, May 4, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    517.15
  - Fox, May 30, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    512.29
  - Fox, Tom, April 21, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    515.2
  - Foyle, 2000s (Box 23, Folder 7)
    512.30
  - Fraise, Bill, May 14, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Friase, Willard, June 5, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    512.31
  - Fraize, Bill, January 17, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Fraize, Barbara, June 7, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Fraize, Barbara, June 7, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Fraser, Jeanne, May 7, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Fraser, Jeanne, June 7, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Frasier, Jim, January 14, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Freeman, Baba, June 10, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Freeman, Baba, June 10, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Freeman, Baba, May 28, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    512.32
  - Fried, Madeline, April 29, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    516.14
  - Frohm, Monte E., December 18, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    452.35
  - Fulkenson, Cate, May 21, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Funk, Marianna, January 1, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    452.36
  - Furniss, Martha, may 25, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Furniss, Martha, June 7, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Furniss, Martha, June 7, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Gallagher, Kevin, June 10, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    512.33
  - Garcia, Robert, June 5, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Garcia, Albert and Dharm Shing, April 6 and 10, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    516.20
  - Garcia, Jay, April 28, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    518.14
  - Garcia, Martha, June 7, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Garison, Elana, May 3, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    517.17
  - Garner, Larry, January 20, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Garten, Craig, June 2, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Gauthier, Jim, June 2, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Gerstein, Susan, May 5, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Gerstein, Susan, May 5, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Gerstein, Suzanne, November 13, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    453.1
  - Gerstein, Susan, April 16, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    516.9
  - Gerstein, Bob, January 10, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Gerstein, Susan, January 8, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Gerstein, Susan, May 11, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Geter, Judy, May 11, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Ghadery, Fred, May 20, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Gibson, Stuart, May 6, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Gibson, Stuart, May 6, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Gildea, Melissa, June 5, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Glaze, Tom, April 10, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    517.14
  - Gleason, Joe, April 22, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    516.8
  - Glennon, Elizabeth, June 8, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Glennon, Elizabeth, June 8, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    512.34
  - Glennon, Elizabeth, June 8, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Glynn, Stephane, May 11, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Gocek, Nancy, April 26, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    515.13
  - Gohrband, Chris, May 6, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Goldfarb, Elizabeth, May 3, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Golembiewski, Gary, May 25, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Goldstein, Larry, June 1, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    512.35
  - Gonzalez, Leah, December 9, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    453.2
  - Gooding-Silverwood, Rozanne, June 11, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Gooding-Silverwood, Rozanne, 2000s (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Gordon, Stephanie, May 28, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Gordon, Lisa, June 13, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Gordon, Leila, June 11, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Gordon, Leila, December 16, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Gordon, Leila, June 10, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Gordon, Leila, 2000s (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Gorski, Maria, February 25, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Graham, Renee, May 15, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Grant, Alex and Jay, May 2, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Graves, Ellen, May 2, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Graves, Ellen, 2000s (Box 27, Folder 10)
    512.36
  - Greadick, Lisa, June 13, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Greene, Vicki, January 16, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Greenacre, David, May 24, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Greenberg, Gail, January 7, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Grein, Tom, January 12, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Grey, 2000s (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Grieshaber, Margaret, 2000s (Box 27, Folder 17)
    453.3
  - Griggs, Barbara, May 11, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Griggs, Barbara, May 11, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Grillo, 2000s (Box 27, Folder 20)
    512.37
  - Grose, Richard, May 28, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Groves, Lisa, June 7, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Groves, Lisa, June 7, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Grubisich, Tom, December 11, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    453.4
  - Grubisich, Tom, January 2, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Grubisich, Tom, January 11, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    505.15
  - Grubisich, Tom, June 1, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    512.38
  - Grussmeyer, Dotzie, April 21, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    517.4
  - Guilfoyle, Sally, June 6, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Guilfoyle, Sally, 2000s (Box 28, Folder 10)
    512.39
  - Guilfoyle, Sally, June 6, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Guinee, Barbara, December 5, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    453.5
  - Gularia, May 29, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Gulick, Peter, May 28, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Guinee, Barbara, June 7, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Guinee, Barbara, June 9, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Guinee, Barbara, January 15, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    505.16
  - Gusdorf, Lori, 2000s (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Gusdorf, Lori, June 14, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Gustein, Susan, May 28, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Guthrie, Michael, May 2, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Guthrie, Michael, May 12, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Guy, Ed, May 30, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Haas, David, January 27, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    505.17
  - Haas, Sandy, May 27, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Hagelis, Al, January 7, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    505.18
  - Hagelis, Al, December 17, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    453.6
  - Hak, Erol, May 3, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Hall, Janet, June 2, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Hall, Bruce, May 3, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Halpin, Julie, January 16, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    505.19
  - Hammann, Robert, June 1, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Hammer, Marlene, June 4, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Handerahan, Leigh P., June 10, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Handerahan, Leigh, June 11, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Hanely, Kate, June 4, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Hanely, Kate, June 4, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Hanley, Katherine, June 4, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Hanlon, Harriet, June 5, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Hannigan, Vera, June 7, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Hannigan, Vera, January 28, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    505.20
  - Hannigan, Vera, June 7, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Harahan, Eileen Berry, December 17, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    453.7
  - Harding, Barbara, January 13, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    453.8
  - Harding, Jane, May 12, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Harding, Wayne, April 1, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    518.17
  - Harley, Katherine, June 4, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Harned, 2000s (Box 30, Folder 13)
    512.40
  - Harrington, Mary, April 9, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    515.10
  - Harris, Nancy, June 9, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    512.41
  - Harris, James, May 22, 2008 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Harris, Mary Ellen, December 19, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    453.9
  - Hartley, Mark, May 27, 2008 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Haus, Lora, December 29, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    453.10
  - Hauser, Kathy, December 30, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    453.11
  - Hauter, Tanja, May 30, 2007 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Havill, Adrien, May 1, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Hay, Eleanor, May 30, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Hays, Dick and Janet, May 18, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Heilman, Betsy, May 30, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Henri, Axel, May 6, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Herd, Charlotte, June 7, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Herold, Alda, May 16, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    512.42
  - Herron, Robert, April 20, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    517.26
  - Heron, Andrew, June 4, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Hersey, Paul and Jane, May 11, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Hester, John, June 6, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Hester, John, June 6, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Hiatt,t William, May 25, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Hill, Bill, June 15, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    512.43
  - Hill, Matthew, May 17, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Hine, Dan, April 16, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    518.5
  - Hirsch, Donna, 2000s (Box 32, Folder 2)
    515.18
  - Hjalmarson, Margret, 2000s (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Hjalmarson, Margret, June 9, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Hodgson, Brad, April 25, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    518.1
  - Holmquist, Karen, 200s (Box 32, Folder 6)
    512.44
  - Hopson, Haywood, May 6, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Horton, John, April 16, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    515.9
  - Hotz, Peter, January 2, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    453.12
  - Housley, Steve, April 15, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    515.23
  - Howard, Bob, January 6, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    453.13
  - Howell, Janet-Senator, June 6, 2008 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Howell, Janet, June 8, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    512.45
  - Howell, Janet-Senator, 2000s (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Howell, Janet, May 17, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Howell, Janet, May 15, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Hoyos, Carolina, June 4, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Hsieh, Jerry, April 12, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    516.18
  - Hudgins, Catherine, June 7, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Hudgins, Cathy, May 1, ,2002 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Hudgins, Catherine, June 8, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Hudgins, Catherine, May 23, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    512.46
  - Hudgins, Catherine, June 7, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Hudgins, Cathy, May 1, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Hughes, Donna Rice, June 9, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Humphrey, Madeleine, May 2002 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Hunter, Carol, January 21, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    505.21
  - Hunter, John, June 5, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    513.01
  - Husch, Denis, January 6, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    505.22
  - Husted, Wesley, R., December 29, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    505.23
  - Huycke, Don, May 3, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Hyman, Joseph, May 7, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Hyman, Joe, May 7, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Ifert, Linda, May 6, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Illchyshyn, Irene, May 5, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Illchyshyn, Irene, 2000s (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Impellizzeri, Agatino, May 5, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Ingerbritsen, Karl, December 9, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    453.14
  - Ingebristen, Karl, June 10, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    513.02
  - Ingebritsen, Karl, May 26, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Ipsen, Marcia, May 27, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Ireland, Judy, December 18, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    453.15
  - Irons-Lecesne, Brenda, June 7, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Irons-Lecesne, Brenda, June 7, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Irwin, Margaret, May 27, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Irwin, Margaret, May 27, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Isaacs, Benno, 2000s (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Isaacs, Benno, May 6, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Isaacs, Carol, June 9, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Isaacs, Carol, May 9, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Isaacs, Carol, June 11, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Isaacs, Carol, May 18, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Jackson, Deborah, June 10, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Jackson, Debra, May 1, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Jackson, Mary, May 16, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Jackson, Mary, May 16, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Jackson, William, January 12, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    505.24
  - Jaffee, Jerry, January 10, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    505.25
  - James, Kim D., April 16, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    511.11
  - Jasmann, June 2, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Jennings, Olivia, 2000s (Box 35, Folder 9)
    513.03
  - Jeter, June 17, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Jeter, Lerory, May 24, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Jiang, May 19, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - John, Bethanie, May 17, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - John, Sandra, June 11, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - John, Sandra, June 9, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Jones, Lillian Adelle, May 1, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Jones, Lillian Adelle, May 1, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Jones, Suzi, January 21, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    505.26
  - Jones, Susan, December 3, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    453.16
  - Jones, Suzi, May 4, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Joyce, Ruby, May 1, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Kafe, Shara, 2000s (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Kain, George, December 28, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    453.17
  - Kamstra, Thomas, April 14, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    517.9
  - Kane, Patrick, May 4, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Kane, Patrick, January 9, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    505.27
  - Kane, Marshall, April 16, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    517.28
  - Kane, Patrick, May 12, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Kane, Patrick, April 23, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    517.5
  - Kaplan, Mark, May 8, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Karam, Emily, December 26, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    453.18
  - Kasprowicz, Joan, June 8, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    513.04
  - Katz, Bernard, June 7, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    513.05
  - Katz, Annie, June 11, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Katz, Annie, June 11, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Kauffman, Peter, April 20, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    515.31
  - Kee, Dorry, June 8, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Kee, Donald, May 25, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Kee, Dorry, June 9, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Keefe, Bill, June 11, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    513.06
  - Kelleher, Kenneth, June 2000 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    513.07
  - Kendall, Rosemary, May 28, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    513.08
  - Kennedy, Patty, June 6, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    513.09
  - Kern, Dennis, May 14, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Kern, Dennis, May 14, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Kfloury, Jorge, 200s (Box 37, Folder 18)
    517.6
  - Khan, Sumi, May 28, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Kidwell, Fran, June 4, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    513.10
  - Killpack, Beverley, June 7, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Killpack, Beverley, June 3, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Kim, Jerry, June 8, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Kirby, Thomas and Kathleen, May 20, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Kirkpatrick, Melissa, May 4, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Kirkpatrick, Melissa, May 4, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Kirwan, James, 2000s (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Kline, Sally, May 15, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Klinker, L.M., May 27, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Knapp, May 13, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Knox, June 9, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Knox, Joyce, June 9, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Kolcun, Curt, May 19, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Kolva, Jim, June 10, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Koval, Frank, May 29, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Kredel, Nancy, June 8, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Krocker, Michelle, May 25, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Kwan, Val, May 8, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Kyle, Franklin, May 23, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - LaCroix, Ruth, January 12, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    504.33
  - Lair, Jim, June 7, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    513.11
  - Lambert, May 20, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Lamar, Ann, June 8, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    513.12
  - Lamkin, Kathy, May 13, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Lamkin, Burton, May 3, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Lamkin, Kathryne, June 6, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Lamkin, Kathy, May 13, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Lamkin, Burton, May 3, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Lamkin, Kathryne, June 9, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Lange, Herta, May 31, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Larson, 2000s (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Larson, Nancy, June 3, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Larson, Sarah, June 12, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Larson, Sarah, June 9, 2006 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Larson, Nancy, May 8, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Larson, Sarah, 2000s (Box 40, Folder 3)
    453.20
  - Larson, Nancy, December 10, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    453.19
  - Larson, Nancy, June 3, 2006 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Larson, Sarah, January 16, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    505.28
  - Larson, Sarah, June 12, 2006 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Lasansky, Anita, June 5, 2006 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Lasansky, Anita, June 5, 2006 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - LaValley, Mary Beth, June 4, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Lawrence, Calvin E., May 15, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Lawson, Karen, May 7, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Lazear, Walter, May 28, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Leary, Joe, January 10, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    505.29
  - LeCesne, Alverez, June 6, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    513.13
  - LeCesne, ALvarez, April 29, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Le Le, June 3, 2007 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Lee, Takicha, June 3, 2007 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Lee, Takicha, June 3, 2007 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Lee, Kyungthen, June 2, 2008 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Lee, Hyeon Kon, May 31, 2007 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Lewis, David, May 14, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Lewis, David, May 14, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Lewis, Earl, May 9, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Lewis, Susan, December 10, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    453.22
  - Lewis, Earl, February 6, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    453.21
  - Ley, Judith, April 24, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    516.13
  - Lilienthal, Lynn, June 10, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Lilienthal, Philip H., December 21, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    453.24
  - Lilienthal, Andy, December 15, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    453.23
  - Lilienthal, Lynn, June 11, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Lindholm, Brenda, June 7, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Link, Jolee Loveland, May 10, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Lik, Jolee Loveland, May 11, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Linn, Liz, June 1, 2007 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Lister, Harry, May 30, 2008 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Loehr, Dan, May 26, 2008 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Loftis, Sandy, February 22, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    505.30
  - Lombardozzi, Lisa, January 12, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    505.31
  - Long, Blenda, April 12, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    512.4
  - Looney, Martha, April 18, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    516.25
  - Lord, Diane, 2000s (Box 42, Folder 7)
    513.14
  - Lorens, Eric, April 21, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    512.6
  - Lovaas, John, May 15, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Love, Lezlie, June 9, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Love, Lezlie, June 9, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Love, Adam, April 10, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    518.2
  - Lovett, Tlaire, May 8, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Lovett, Denver, September 5, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Lowe, Earl and Pat, May 12, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Lowery, Brian, April 9, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    515.6
  - Lucas, Cate, June 2, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    513.15
  - Lundy, Mary, January 21, 1998 and February 5, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    505.32
  - Lyle, Marilyn, May 30, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    513.16
  - Mac, June 10, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - MacDicken, Eric and Caroline, May 2, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - MacIntyre, Pat, 2000s (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - MacIntyre, Pat, June 7, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    513.17
  - MacIntyre, Pat, June 10, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - MacIntyre, pat, May 4, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - MacIntyre, Pat, 2000s (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Maddox, Mary, May 4, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Majette, Dean, January 11, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    505.33
  - Male, Lois, June 8, 2008 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Malendez, Freddie, March 27, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    515.12
  - Malcolm, Susan, June 6, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Malone, Bea, May 5, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Malovich, Mary, June 9, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Mandaro, Mary Grace, June 11, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Mandaro, Mary Grace, June 11, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Mangold, Harry, 2000s (Box 44, Folder 7)
    453.25
  - Marchand, Alice, April 6, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    515.24
  - Mark, Joseph, May 9, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Markell, Joe, May 7, 2004 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Marquardt, Eveline, 2000s (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Marshall, Ryan, May 6, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Martin, Mike, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    513.18
  - Martin, Mike, June 1, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    513.19
  - Mashinski, Bill, May 3, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Masloohi, Mustapha, April 10, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    518.10
  - Mason-Boyd, Mary, May 8, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Matthews, Katina, June 5, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Mathis, David, May 30, 2008 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Mayer, Valerie, 2000s (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - McArdle, Geri, May 5, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - McCallister, April 13, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    515.11
  - McCloskey, Anne, May 14, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - McCracken, Pat and Jay, June 9, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    513.21
  - McDevitt, Martia, May 10, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - McDevitt, Marcia, June 7, 2006 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - McDevitt, Marcia, June 19, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - McDevitt, Marcia, June 7, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - McDonald, Karen, June 11, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    513.22
  - McDonnell, June, April 13, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    515.8
  - McFalls, Jessica, June 8, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    513.20
  - McGinn, Sheri, May 14, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 6)